gistreel.com 2019-04-12

# Privacy Policy - GistReel

### Privacy Policy

GistReel.Com created this Privacy Statement to demonstrate our commitment to Internet users privacy. The following policy discloses GistReel.Com information collecting, use, and disclosure practices for our Web site. Our employees are required to follow our privacy policies. Those employees who violate our privacy policies are subject to disciplinary measures up to and including termination.

GistReel.Com reserves the right to revise this Privacy Statement at any time at our discretion. Changes to our Privacy Statement will become effective upon posting to our Web site. GistReel.Com will endeavor to notify users of our services of changes in our Privacy Statement.

GistReel.Com collects different types of information in connection with the rendering of our services and the administration of our Web site. GistReel.Com will not voluntarily disclose or sell any information gathered about our users (Personal Information) to third parties for solicitation or other reasons unless you consent, and except as otherwise provided below.

GistReel.Com may from time to time approach its users regarding product, service, and other information, or offers which GistReel.Com feels, based on your Personal Information, may be of interest to our users. If you do not wish to receive such information, you can contact us in the manner provided above. In addition, Personal Information may be released to third parties (i) if GistReel.Com is required by law to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena, or court order; (ii) if release of such information is required in connection with the maintenance and administration or our site; (iii) in the very rare circumstance in which GistReel.Com believes in good faith there is a threat to the physical security of one of our users or others. Although it is GistReel.Com policy to attempt to require our third parties to whom GistReel.Com provides Personal Information to comply with our privacy policies, GistReel.Com cannot guarantee their compliance.

Our additional practices and policies with respect to our collection and usage practices are addressed as follows:

Public Comment System and Community Features – GistReel.Com may use third-party contributors and partners or connect directly to social networks to enhance the user’s experience. To allow this, it is sometimes necessary for us to provide non-public user profile information to certain third-party contributors and partners.

Online Surveys/Polls – From time to time, GistReel.Com Users may answer online surveys through the GistReel.Com Web site. Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (such as their e-mail address). Our surveys are designed to obtain broad demographic information regarding our services and the desires and concerns of our customers and visitors.

Contests – From time to time, GistReel.ComUsers may participate in contests through the GistReel.Com Web site. GistReel.Com runs contests on our site in which GistReel.Com may ask visitors for contact information (such as their e-mail address) and demographic information (such as their zip code, age, or income level).

Outside Ad Company – GistReel.Com may use an outside advertising or marketing company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While GistReel.Com use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner, or text ads are collected by our marketing company, and GistReel.Com does not have access to this information. (For more information on our use of cookies, see the Cookies section below.) In addition, our site may contain links to other Web sites. GistReel.Com does not endorse and are not responsible for the content of third-party Web sites accessed through our site or for any privacy practices with respect to such sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Usage Tracking – Our Web site automatically tracks certain information from Users. This information includes the URL that the User came from, what browser the User is using, and the Users IP address. Many Web sites automatically collect this information. GistReel.Com gathers and uses such information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. As stated above, GistReel.Com will not voluntarily disclose or sell any information gathered about our users (Personal Information) to third parties for solicitation or other reasons unless you consent, and except as otherwise provided above.

Cookies – GistReel.Com may uses cookies on certain pages of our service. Cookies are small pieces of information that your Web browser places on your computers hard drive. Cookies can help us personalize our Web site and provide information that is targeted to the interests of individual Users (so you don’t see the same advertisements repeatedly). GistReel.Com may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to reenter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes.

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change this feature in your browser. The User is always free to decline our cookies if his or her browser permits, although in that case the service may be largely unusable.

Correspondence – If a User sends us personal correspondence, such as e-mails or letters, GistReel.Com may collect such information into a file specific to that User. Users should not send privileged or sensitive materials unless specifically directed, or granted permission, by GistReel.Com or one of its affiliate attorneys.

Regulatory Issues – Due to the existing regulatory environment, GistReel.Com cannot ensure that all of a Users private communications and other Personal Information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), GistReel.Com may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, GistReel.Com can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as GistReel.Com, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. GistReel.Com uses industry standard practices to protect our Users privacy, GistReel.Com does not promise that their personally identifiable information or private communications can remain private.

Security – GistReel.Com is aware of Internet Users concerns about the privacy of their information. Our Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. User information is stored on servers protected by firewall, system-level, and database-level security.

Only those employees of GistReel.Com who require access to data concerning Users are granted access to the data (e.g., marketing product managers, system administrators, customer service representatives, and engineering personnel). Access to User data by employees is further limited by being solely available through a dedicated administrative interface and through use of a restricted user ID and password. In addition, every employee of GistReel.Com is required to sign GistReel.Com’s standard Nondisclosure and Developments Agreement that requires employees to keep User data confidential. GistReel.Com’s internal Web security policies are reviewed and revised on a regular basis.

International Information – Personal data that you have voluntarily entered is delivered electronically to servers located in the United States. By using GistReel.Com, you consent to the transfer of this data and to GistReel.Com’s use of such data as outlined in this policy.

Users Consent – Users consent to the collection and use of their information as described herein. Users will be notified by e-mail in the event of any fundamental changes to the uses of information that are described herein.

Data Quality and Access – In accordance with the Fair Information Practices defined by the government, GistReel.Com encourages Users to correct any inaccuracies in personal information that has been previously provided to the Web site. Users may correct or update their information by sending an e-mail to [gistreel@gmail.com](mailto:gistreel@gmail.com)

If we use any content of yours in disregard to your policy, please contact us for take down. We obey every take down request we get on the site.

Feedback – Users may provide feedback (e.g., input and suggestions) to GistReel.Com regarding the GistReel.Com Web site. Users providing feedback must provide their name and e-mail address. Any contact information entered when providing feedback will only be used to acknowledge or respond to that feedback.

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement and policies or your dealings with our Web site, please [**contact us.**](http://gistreel.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us")
